A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Special Events and Activities, Lecture Series FA898
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Special Events and Activities, Lecture Series
1996, 2001-2005
2001-2005
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA898
0.44 Cubic Feet 1 box
1 box.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 600-29
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Lectures and symposia.
China; Medical sciences; Medicine, Preventive; Vivisection; Genetics; DNA; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Medical care; Biology -- Research; Medical research
- Annual Cancer Symposium, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cancer Biology Lectures, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Insight - Talks on Science, Policy, and the Humanities, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Jerry A. Weisbach Lectures, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Joshua A. Lederberg Distinguished Lectures in Molecular Genetics, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Philip Levine Memorial Lectures, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Richard M. Furlaud Distinguished Lectures, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Symposium of Honor of Robert G. Roeder's 60th Birthday, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Symposium on Cellular Regulation in Development, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- William H. Stein Memorial Lecture, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Zanvil A. Cohn Forum on Health Affairs, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)